A Guide to the Records of Central State Hospital, 1874-1961
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Commitment Papers, 1874-1906. (Box 1-107.)
  - 1890.
    - M. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - M. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - N. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - P. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - P. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - R. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - R. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - S. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - S. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - S. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - T. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - T. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - T. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - U. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - W. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - 1891.
    - A. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - A. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - C. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - C. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - C. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - D. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - E. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - F. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - J. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - J. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - K. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - L. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - M. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - M. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - M. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - N. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - O. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - P. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - P. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - P. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - P. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - R. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - R. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - R. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - R. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - T. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - T. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - T. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - U. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - W. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Y. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 1892.
    - A. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - C. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - D-E. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - G-H. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - L. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - P. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Q-R. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - 1893.
    - A. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - B. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - C. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - C. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - C. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - D. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - D. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - E. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - F. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - J. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - J. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - K. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - L. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - L. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - L. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - L. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - M. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - M. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - M. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Mc. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - N. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - P. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - P. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - P. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - R. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - S. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - T. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - T. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Y. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 1894.
    - A. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - A. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - B. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - D. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - D. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - E. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - E. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - F. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - G. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - H. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - H. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - H. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - H. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - I. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - J. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - J. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - J. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - J. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - L. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - M. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - M. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - M. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - M. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - M. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - N-Q. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - R. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - R. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - T. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - T. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - W. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - W. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 1895.
    - A. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - C. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - C. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - D. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - D. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - E. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - F. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - J. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - J. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - L. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - L. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - M. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - M. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - M. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - M. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Mc. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - N. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - P. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - P. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - R. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - S. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - S. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - S. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - T. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - T. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - V. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - 1896.
    - A. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - A. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - B. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - C. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - C. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - C. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - D. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - D. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - E. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - F. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - G. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - J. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - J. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - J. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - K. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - L. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - M. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - M. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - M. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Mc. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - N. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - P. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - R. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - R. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - R. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - S. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - S. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - S. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - S. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - T. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - T. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - T. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - V. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - W. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - W. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - W. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - W. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - W. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Y. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1897.
    - A. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - C. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - D. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - D. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - D. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - E. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - E. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - F. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - G. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - I. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - J. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - K. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - L. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - L. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - M. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - M. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - M. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - M. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - M. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Mc. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - N. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - O. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - O. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - P. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - P. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - P. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - P. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Q. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - R. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - R. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - R. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - S. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - S. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - S. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - S. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - S. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - S. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - T. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - T. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - T. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - U (unknown). (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - V. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - W. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - W. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - W. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - W. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Y. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - 1898.
    - B. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - B. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - C. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - C. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - D. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - D. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - E. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - E. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - F. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - H. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - I. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - J. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - J. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - J. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - K. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - L. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - M. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - M. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Mc. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - N. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - P. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - P. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - P. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - R. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - R. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - S. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - S. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - T. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - T. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - T. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - W. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Y. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - 1899.
    - A. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - C. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - C. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - C. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - D. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - E. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - F. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - G. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - G. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - H. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - J. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - L. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - M. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - M. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - N-O. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - P. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - P. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - P. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - R. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - R. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - S. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - S. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - T. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - T. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - W. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - 1900.
    - A. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - A. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - B. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - C. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - D. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - D. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - D. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - E. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - F. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - G. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - G. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - H. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - H. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - H. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - H. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - I. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - J. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - J. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - J. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - J. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - K. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - L. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - L. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - M. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - M. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - M. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - M. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Mc. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - N. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - O. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - P. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - P. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - R. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - T. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - V. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - W. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - W. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - W. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 1901.
    - A. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - A. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - C. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - D. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - D. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - D. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - E. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - F. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - F. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - H. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - H. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - J. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - K. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - L. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - L. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - M. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - M. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - M. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - M. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Mc. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - N-O. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - P. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - P. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - P. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - R. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - R. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - R. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - R. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - S. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - T. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - T. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - T. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - T. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - V. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Y. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - 1902.
    - A. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - C. (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - D. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - D. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - E. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - E. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - E. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - F. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - F. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - G. (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - G. (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - G. (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - I. (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - H. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - H. (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - H. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - H. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - H. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - J. (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - K. (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - L. (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - L. (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - L. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - M. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - M. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - M. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Mc. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - N. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - O. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - P. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - P. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - P. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - P. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - P. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Q. (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - R. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - R. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - S. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - S. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - S. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - S. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - S. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - T. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - T. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - T. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - T. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - V. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - W. (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - W. (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - W. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - W. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - W. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Y. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - 1903.
    - A. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - A. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - B. (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - B. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - C. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - D. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - D. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - E. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - E. (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - F. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - F. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - F. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - G. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - G. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - H. (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - H. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - H. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - J. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - K. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - K. (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - L. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - L. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - M. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - M. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - M. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - M. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Mc. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - N-O. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - P. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - P. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - P. (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Q. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - R. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - R. (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - R. (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - R. (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - S. (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - S. (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - S. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - S. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - T. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - T. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - T. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - V. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - W. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - 1904.
    - A. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - A. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - B. (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - C. (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - C. (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - C. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - C. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - C. (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - C. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - C. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - D. (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - D. (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - D. (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - E. (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - E. (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - E. (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - E. (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - F. (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - F. (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - G. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - G. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - G. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - G. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - G. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - H. (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - J. (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - K. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - L. (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - L. (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - L. (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - M. (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - M. (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - M. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - M. (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - M. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - M. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Mc. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - N. (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - O. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - P. (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - P. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - P. (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - R. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - R. (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - R. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - R. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - S. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - T. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - T. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - T. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - T. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - V. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - W. (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Y. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - 1905.
    - A. (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - A. (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - B. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - B. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - B. (Box 95, Folder 3)